<DialogCollection>
    <Dialogs>
        <Dialog id="0" pilot="1">
        	<Talk>It's the black hole that you destined for. It's the beginning of the SM project.Hopefully you can endure it successfully.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="1" pilot="2">
            <Talk>A SM projet??? Seriously??? What are you thinking in the space? Introducing Grils Generation widly to the space? It doesn't work without Jessica then..</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="2" pilot="3">
            <Talk>긴You don't have to be nervous of going through the balck hole. It's a part of SM project. It's a project that leaving the earth that people can't longer live and reconstruct a part of its DNA. It's called "Sorry mother".</Talk>
        </Dialog>     
        <Dialog id="3" pilot="2">
            <Talk>Ahh, you were talking about the reconstructing project of the earth. Isn't it time for the living creatures on the space probe shoot out the DNA? We should pray for the last wise decision of the mankind. </Talk>
        </Dialog>       
        <Dialog id="4" pilot="3">
            <Talk>What's the importance of taking DNA out since the earth is going to be destoyed.</Talk>
        </Dialog>       
        <Dialog id="5" pilot="1">
            <Talk>The people who suggested the earth reconstruction project disagreed with leving the human DNA. Beacause people like Noah doesn't exist anymore was their reason.</Talk>
        </Dialog>       
        <Dialog id="6" pilot="3">
            <Talk>The project has has been authorized with taking huge capitalists because this project can be end with their money support.</Talk>
        </Dialog>       
        <Dialog id="7" pilot="2">
        	<Talk>Then the human DNA on here is belong to rich or very talented people. It's some what bitter even there were no other options.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="8" pilot="1">
        	<Talk>You don't have to be sad because there is a secret project from the first proposer named 'Kdragon' of this project . Now I'm free to talk aout it since I'm out of the earth. The DNA on this space probe has been changed secretly.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="9" pilot="2">
        	<Talk> What? Can it happen? Then who's DNA is on? and on what standard??? One person can decide all like that?</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="10" pilot="3">
        	<Talk>Like I said. It was hard to find an alive man like Noah from the earth. But there were some from the dead ones.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="11" pilot="2">
        	<Talk>eople who passed away? Maybe he left his DNA seretly? I'm talking about that 'Kdragon' or 'Korea Dragon??'</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="12" pilot="3">
        	<Talk>Hmm.. He throws out about hundreds million a day. There's nothing to leave.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="13" pilot="3">
        	<Talk>The role of mankind has been competed since the spear of longinus has been left on the moon. I feel so sorry for myself leaving the earth before seeing Rei is being cloned.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="14" pilot="1">
            <Talk>Stop talking nonsense. Religion, politic, education.. nothing made difference when the earth was being coverd with blood. I thought the people who sacrificed themselves for others are the right ones for the new earth. So I have been collected their DNA. I'm sending it to every black hole that I'm passing through. </Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="15" pilot="2">
            <Talk>Is our choice absolutely right? Three of us won't have chance to see the world on the new planet. I still don't understand why I took the people on the space probe. They were unnecessary anyway.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="16" pilot="4">
            <Talk>That is for me to learn the last minute of human being. To write down the end of mankind. It's all messed up ups and downs. There should be one person who smells like honey.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="17" pilot="3">
            <Talk>Maybe it's not useful on the space probe, but I have a  special talent of leaving a few parts when assembling or disassembling the machines. Let me check with you Marvin?
</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="18" pilot="4">
            <Talk>The number of my parts is 42 multiplier of 42 which is perfect. So don't you ever touch my body with your big fingers.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="19" pilot="3">
            <Talk>So why don't we check with the list of the people who were sent to the future of mankind?</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="20" pilot="4">
            <Talk> The DNA from the earth is not independent. We chose the DNA who do what A.I won't when there is a limit that human can. We A.I can't learn something that we never can do or understand.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="21" pilot="4">
            <Talk>For example, jumping into a railroad to save people, or running into a burning building with a sense of duty when the time of danger.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="22" pilot="4">
            <Talk>There is a young man who was trying to save a woman from a suspicious guy with a knife and died.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="23" pilot="4">
            <Talk>It's like the energy of the young female school teacher who died while saving students from a sinking ship. The feeling of reliance is hard for A.I to understand.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="24" pilot="2">
            <Talk>So, can the mankind strat again at the new colony? Such as meeting other living creatures or civilize themselves and coming back to the earth.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="25" pilot="4">
            <Talk>Because of the low possibility, there is a project that separately saves DNA of the earth. They are called as hotels and sperm bank. The possibility is really low. Even if someone revisits the earth, he won't find anything on the cold dead earth.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="26" pilot="4">
            <Talk>That's one of the most interesting things as an A.I. People who are really intelligent also believe in miracles. The word "hope" may made mankind like this.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="27" pilot="4">
            <Talk>I'm the only one who can reach to the new colonized planet. DNA is not going to do a huge role. The good news is I can still have your memories even after billion years. Except, it's sad to remember the last memory of mankind is A cup.(small bra size korean joke)</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="28" pilot="2">
            <Talk>It's better to end the future og mankind here. I'll write down about the last A.I of mankind finished by A cups on the space probe!</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="29" pilot="1">
            <Talk>What will happen to the eateh after mankind disappears? Can someone rememer the mankind?</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="30" pilot="4">
            <Talk>There will be no chance before the earth destroys. The earth has 17 hundred million years more and mankind has a few thousands years more. We're civilized to move to another planet but there's not enough time to come back to the earth.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="31" pilot="4">
            <Talk>When comparing a single cell evolved to a dinosaur, the evolution of human is nothing. Moreover, mankind itself hasn't evolved that much. Both physically and mentally.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="32" pilot="4">
            <Talk>Our new planet is similar. We found a self growing planet with good environments. The DNA we're sending is not worth as one drop of paint in the ocean. Mankind started this project with a hope that there will be miracle of one drop changes the color of the ocean. </Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="33" pilot="1">
            <Talk>Mankind evolved with hope and want to complete the end with a hope.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="34" pilot="2">
            <Talk>If the human DNA civilizes the new colony, I hope there is only one God. Then they might not kill each other under the name of religions.</Talk>
        </Dialog>
        <Dialog id="35" pilot="4">
            <Talk>I'm the one who's going to do that role. They will see me with their eyes, and I'll show them miracles. So at least they can't think of other Gods. The name of the religion will be "The mother from darkness". It will of course be called in there language.</Talk>
        </Dialog>

    </Dialogs>
</DialogCollection>